This is a routine pursuit.
Main Force repeats,
this is a routine pursuit. Code 44.
Listen, you tell them we need some help.
This should be an open-code blitz,
and you know it.
You have your information.
Come on, sweetheart,
this one's a heavyweight!
Main Force repeats,
you have your information.
This is a routine pursuit.
Please report to Big Bopper.
March Hare to Big Bopper.
Assist on Code 3 red alert.
Big Bopper. Gotcha, Hare.
What's going down?
- We've got a cop-killer.
- You're kidding!
Be warned, Sarse, this is non-compliance.
The Main Force will not tolerate
such action.
This is not a Code 3 red alert. This
pursuit is designated a standard Code 44.
Please respond only to that code.
Code 44 indicates no requirement
for a blockade.
A Pursuit Special has been stolen.
Hall Captain Fifi Macaffee does not
like this any more than you.
However, we must not compromise
territorial range.
Remember that only
by following instructions
can we hope to maintain
a successful highway program.
Ah, Jesus!
March Hare to Big Bopper.
We're three minutes off the intersection.
- Reckon you can make it?
- We'll make it! Move over!
- Roop!
- I'm driving!
Not this again! I've been assigned!
Wait a second, you son of a bitch.
I'm supposed to drive this heap!
Where do you get off, huh?
Where do you get off?
Hey, Sarse, what's the form on this guy?
A weirdo bike jockey.
A few hours ago, down in Sun City,
he goes berserk.
Breaks custody, wastes a rookie
and takes off in a Pursuit Special.
We've been on him ever since.
This one's as flaky as they come, Roop.
I've seen the style before.
It's terminal psychotic.
What's he driving?
That's what hurts. It's one of our V8s.
Pursuit Special on methane. Super hot!
Okay, we're about half a mile
off Anarchy Road.
You'll see him any minute now.
Rip the guts out of him!
Give it to me, Jesus!
See him yet?
Got it!
- I'm gonna blow him away!
- Goddamn him!
I'm gonna ram him!
Move away from the passenger door.
Hey, fellas, you okay?
Acknowledge, Big Bopper.
Acknowledge, are you okay?
Roop? Charlie?
Do you see me, Toecutter?
Do you see me, man?
Keep going. Keep going, we're okay.
We got you, we're going.
Born with a steering wheel in his hand,
and lead in his foot.
I am the Nightrider
cruising at the speed of fright!
I am the Nightrider,
and I ain't never coming back!
I'm a fuel-injected suicide machine!
Do you hear me, pigs? Do you hear me,
Bronze pigs? Do you hear me, Bronze?
I think we're still mobile.
For Christ's sake, shove over!
You're blaspheming again.
I don't have to work with a blasphemer.
Well, you missed us, pig! Hey,
big brother, this is The Nightrider...
Big Bopper to March Hare.
We're still in the game, okay?
Understand this.
That Scag and his floozie
they're gonna die!
Code 44, standard pursuit.
Please respond.
MFP to Gosling One.
Come on, Goose, where are you?
It was like slow motion.
He leaves his seat
and goes through the windshield
headfirst straight into the tree, right,
and then bounces back
through the windshield.
And by the time we got to him,
he was just sitting there
trying to scream
with his face ripped off.
What's the matter?
Not hungry anymore.
Give it here. I'll tell you what...
Christ, they're heading for population!
Now, what's this I hear
about you and Jonathan?
- What about him?
- You were seen with him two nights ago.
So what?
It's, um, this way.
He's gone.
Bastard!
Oh, shit!
You're really gonna get it this time.
He had his indicator on.
Shut up!
No, no, you're not going on.
Stay off the road!
Of course, I'm going on. Shut up!
People's lives are in peril!
What are you doing? You gone nuts?
Do I have him?
Stay off the road!
- I got him! Shut up!
- Stay on him!
Oh, my God.
Watch out!
- Great! Down in one.
- Ha-ha-ha!
I am ready.
I am ready for your best.
Oh, my God, what happened?
I don't know, man. I just got here myself.
Main Force Patrol
we're out of the game
unable to continue pursuit.
You'd better send a meat truck.
Charlie's been hurt bad in the throat.
Hey, Max?
Can you hear me, Max?
Go ahead.
We are 100 percent snafued.
You okay, Goose?
Nothing a year in
the tropics wouldn't fix!
Much damage?
You should see the damage, Bronze! Huh?
Metal damage
brain damage, huh?
You listening, Bronze?
I am the Nightrider!
I'm a fuel-injected suicide machine.
I am a rocker! I am a roller!
I am an out-of-controller!
I am a Nightrider, baby,
and it's me and my Marmaduke,
and we ain't never coming back.
The Toecutter
he knows who I am.
I am the Nightrider!
I am the chosen one,
the mighty hand of vengeance
sent down to strike the unroadworthy!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'm hotter than a rolling dice.
Step right up, chum,
and watch the kid
lay down a rubber road, right to freedom!
What's wrong? Baby, what's wrong?
Tell me what's wrong!
It's going.
There'll be nothing left. It's all gone.
Stop! Stop!
Ah, that feels good.
After three days that feels so good.
I got a right hook in the mouth
this morning.
- Sprog?
- Mm.
I told him to always lead with his left.
You know, I think we've got
a monster on our hands.
Yeah, takes after his old man.
- What's that?
- Monster!
Montazano,
who called himself the Nightrider
had broken from custody
and escaped to the police vehicle.
- You made the news again. Hm.
- Mm.
Who was he?
I don't know.
Just another glory roader, I guess.
Jessie, I told you.
The Goose wants me there early.
What for, he didn't say.
You know the Goose.
Coffee's ready.
I'm not grumpy.
Get out of here.
Okay.
I gotta go.
Hey!
What's that?
Crazy about you.
Penalties against pirate towing-operators
will be stiffened considerably
in the next quarter.
Driver detention will be replaced
by rig confiscation.
Second offenders under the new decree
will be met by state appropriation
of the unauthorized vehicles.
Memorandum Three:
The incidents have been reported recently
in the People's Gazette.
There is to be no dealing in petroleum
by members of the Main Force.
Memorandum Seven:
The Captains of the Hall have
asked that pursuit officers
refrain from using the slang "Bronze"
for the Main Force Patrol.
The word is considered disrespectful,
and citizens should
actively be discouraged from its use.
Kick it in the guts, Barry.
She's the last of the V8s.
You can shut the gate on this one.
It's the Duck's guts.
Yeah, she's the last of the V8s.
Sucks nitro.
Phase 4, head, twin overhead cam.
- Tell him about the Blower.
- Six hundred horsepower.
The Blower! The Blower, man!
- He's in a coma, man!
- He loves it.
Okay.
How the hell did you
get all this together?
It just happened, Max, you know?
A piece from here and a piece from there.
- So easy?
- Yeah.
Come on, Max. You've seen it, you've heard
it, and you're still asking questions?
Code Samurai 1, progress 46
on multiple fatal. Code Samurai 1...
When do we go for a ride?
Animal!
I think we've got him.
I hope so.
Yeah, we've got him.
Your top pursuit man wants
to quit the road,
and we have to seduce him with candy?
People don't believe in heroes anymore.
I know, Macaffee.
You want to give them back their heroes.
You will not try this one on me again.
I do not enjoy wasting money.
Goodbye,
and good luck!
Thanks, Labatouche
you're a real human being.
Shut up! Get out of here!
Get out of my way!
The old meat grinder's
humming tonight, eh?
Yeah, Max took out a couple
of crazies just now, that's all.
Hey, shut up!
Hey, Max, another one for your books, eh?
You eaten yet?
No, not yet. I'll pick up something later.
Hey, that, um, Code 3
you ran down a few days ago.
- The Nightrider?
- The Nightrider, yeah.
- Got a problem.
- What's that?
Well, his friends.
Word is they're out to get you.
- Scoot jockeys?
- Yeah, nomad trash.
Hmm.
Well, I'll add it to my threat collection.
Ha, ha. Good boy, Max. You're a good boy.
Hey, come on.
Good afternoon.
We're here to meet a friend.
Coming on the train.
Nothing coming on the train
except a couple of crates and a, heh
coffin.
Our friend.
You'll have to see the agent
and sign the papers.
Where do we find
this agent?
Wait.
That must be your friend over there.
Didn't leave much of him.
Must have cut his heart out, huh?
Yeah. That's what I meant.
Poor bastard.
The Nightrider
that is his name.
The Nightrider.
Remember him
when you look at the night sky.
I will.
Take your hat off.
Anything you say.
Anything I say.
What a wonderful philosophy you have.
Take him away.
Bubba. Johnny.
Whoo!
Oh!
- Push me, shove you!
- Oh, yeah? Says who?
Push me, shove you,
push me, shove you, push me, shove you!
Come on! Nightrider!
Nightrider!
Don't worry.
Anyway, my name is Jim Goose.
Rockatansky, here.
We have incident at Wee Jerusalem.
Nomad bikers, bulk trouble.
Okay, we're on it. We're going.
Goose, let's go.
So long. Sorry, we gotta go.
What's this?
It's a get-out-of-jail-free card.
- Any more details?
- No.
Okay, we're going.
- Max, see what I see?
- Yeah.
Hey, fella, stop!
Hey, fella!
Ah.
Hey, fella, stop!
What a turkey!
Hey, fella, you're a turkey,
you know that?
We'll come back for him later.
There's more up ahead.
Nightrider.
See to her.
Bronze!
Gonna get you!
Okay.
It's all right. No one's gonna hurt you.
It's all right.
This one's whacked out of his skull.
Whacked right out of his skull, man!
He ain't never coming back. Whoo!
It's all right.
I'm gonna let this go now.
I know you're a frightened girl,
but no one's gonna hurt you anymore.
My name's Jim Goose,
and everything's gonna be all right.
Fifi wants
no recurrence of the Sun City incident.
Warn people off the roads.
Use your sirens.
The Nightrider!
- Hey, Jimbo.
- Yeah?
- Remember that Code 3?
- Yeah, sure.
Remember him when you look up!
When you look...
Nightrider!
Well, well, well!
Johnny the Boy is still at the wreck.
Stoned again.
He's never gonna learn.
But we are going to teach him, Bubba.
You are going back for him.
No way! Not me, not for him!
But it's not for him.
It's for me, Bubba.
You're wasting your time!
The Scag don't rate!
He's nothing like the Nightrider!
MFP Code 1.
Captain Macaffee in convoy from
the court house to the Halls of Justice.
Hey, mister!
What happened to the car?
What do you think happened?
Looks like it was chewed up and spat out.
Perhaps it was the result of anxiety.
Hey, Roop.
Stay here, man.
I think they're out there.
Take your time, Charlie.
We got plenty of it.
I can see the Interceptor.
What do you say, Scag?
Got no place special to go, huh?
We'd better prep him.
Scag, did you bring your toothbrush?
- You'll have to sit on the Goose.
- Why?
- No contest.
- Damn!
Hey, Fif! What's going on?
- What happened?
- Let him go.
What's he mean, "Let him go"?
Who's this?
- Keep out of this.
- What's going on?
No one showed, okay?
Forget it, Charlie. Just let him go.
No one showed. No one.
What's he mean, "No one showed"?
They didn't show.
Nobody! The punks didn't show.
The girl didn't show,
the townspeople didn't show.
Nobody showed!
- We're screwed!
- Don't touch me!
What do you mean, "No one showed"?
Where were you, man?
It means, old man,
you haven't got a case. No contest.
Jesus Christ! You're not gonna
let him walk out the door, Fifi?
That's exactly what you'll do!
- Shut up, Ralphie!
- Keep going, Charlie! Keep going!
Hey, Bronze, look at you
a cripple and a mute!
He sings, and I tap-dance!
Hey, you know what you are?
You are, you're a...
The courts will hear about this, I promise
you! The courts will hear about this disgrace!
- This man is grossly offensive!
- Out of my way!
Get him out of here, Max!
- I can make a case of it!
- No one filed a complaint!
You saw what they did to that girl!
For God's sake, she was the town pump!
He's my prisoner,
and he's not walking out that door!
Get him out of here!
Who is this guy?
Goose, settle down, boy.
Come on, boy.
Look, they're laughing at us!
Can't you see they're laughing at us?
I don't believe this!
See you later, Goose.
It's been a pleasure.
Get in the car, go home.
We don't want you around here.
Hey, Goose!
You can't do anything about it!
We know who you are, Bronze!
We'll see you on the road, Scag!
See you on the road,
like we saw the Nightrider!
We remember the Nightrider,
and we know who you are!
Okay.
So long as the paperwork is clean,
you boys can do what you like out there.
Here he is, the walking armpit! Ha-ha-ha!
There's a fire in my belly,
and she's the woman to put it out.
Off, brute, this angel's hot in
the tubes for me!
Yee-ha!
I'm on fire!
Joviality is a game of children.
She's mine. I should have been
a surgeon with these hands.
Mudguts, get out of there!
Cundalini, put her against the post.
We have a problem here.
She is not what she seems.
Bubba Zanetti has it on good authority
she's sent by the Bronze,
full of treachery.
The Bronze kill our pride.
If you're going to waste the Bronze,
you gotta do it big!
You just don't have the style,
do you, chicken shit?
Goes to water on a dummy.
It's all right, you'll get your chance!
You'll get your chance.
It's all right. Hm? It's okay.
It's okay.
Just remember
to keep your sweet
sweet mouth shut!
Whoo!
Gosling One. Code 3 in progress.
We have a curfew violation.
Lookin' for some juice
On this side of town
Mister, won't you show the way?
Tryin' to get around
Only one thought left Makes me come alive
And that is you and me side by side
On the licorice ride
Motorbikes and leather men
Take me to the edge of the dream
Hold on tight Though, it sure feels right
Stick to you like a tie on a licorice ride
Yeah, baby.
Welcome, Main Force units,
to three day Angel Patrol.
Nice to have you back, Big Boppa Two.
MFP, copy.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, it's the Goose.
You're a lucky boy.
Didn't even get road rash.
Hey, Midge
don't write off the Goose
until you see the box
going into the hole.
Yeah, well don't wreck my truck now.
- I'll bring it back tomorrow.
- Yeah, no hurry.
Hey, sure you're all right?
Couldn't be righter.
Jimmy the Goose,
larger than life and twice as ugly!
Light me, Johnny.
Light another.
Hey.
This is the threshold moment, Johnny.
Step through.
Toecutter, this isn't what I want.
Light it! Light it, Johnny, for me.
The Bronze,
they keep you from being proud.
Look at him. He looks silly,
doesn't he, upside down?
Do it for freedom and the Nightrider!
- I can't!
- Throw it!
- No!
- You scum-sucking trash!
Throw it!
Max. Max.
Max.
Max! Hey, Max.
That thing in there
that's not the Goose. No way!
I was hungry.
Peanut butter and honey.
I just can't get it clear in my head,
Jess.
He was so full of living, you know.
He ran the franchise on it.
Now there's nothing.
Here I am trying to put sense to it
when I know there isn't any.
I'll be all right,
once I get it clear in my head.
All vehicle repairs
must be authorized by the Hall Captains.
Officers may not deal directly
with underground mechanics.
Doing so is an offense.
Fif.
- What's this?
- I'm through.
- Again?
- No, not again.
- I'm through. I'm quitting.
- Sit down.
No, I didn't come here to discuss it,
I came to say it. I'm through.
Now just a minute!
So the Goose bought it.
But that's the way
he always came at the world.
You're wrong.
Max, you'd be the first to admit
it was long overdue.
All right, I'll tell you how it is.
You're a winner, Max.
You're the top shelf, and I won't lose you
because of some crazy notion about quitting!
They say that people don't believe
in heroes anymore.
Well, damn them!
You and me, Max
we're gonna give them back their heroes.
Ah, Fif, do you really expect me
to go for that crap?
You gotta admit, I sounded
good there for a minute, eh?
Bye, Fifi.
Hey, come on, do you want me to beg?
Do you want me on my knees crying?
- Ha, ha.
- Now just a minute...
Give me a reason.
- I'm scared, Fif.
- Ugh.
Do you know why?
It's that rat circus out there.
I'm beginning to enjoy it.
What is this, funny week?
Any longer out on that road,
and I'm one of them, you know?
A terminal crazy.
Only, I've got a bronze badge
to say I'm one of the good guys.
You know what I'm trying to say?
I'll tell you what I'll do.
Take off a few weeks, huh?
Grow yourself a beard.
Draw flies.
Just think about it for a while.
If you still feel the same way when
you come back, that's okay by me.
Go on.
I'm not gonna change my mind.
Get out of here, before I decide
to come with you, huh? Ha, ha.
Bye, Fif. Thanks.
You'll be back, Rockatansky!
You're hooked, Max,
and you know it!
I've never been able to say things to you,
Jess. About how I feel.
Guess I always counted
on you understanding.
When I was a kid
me and my father used to go
for long walks.
I remember staring down at his shoes.
They were special shoes. Brown.
And he always kept them real shiny.
He was tall,
and he used to take long strides.
And there I'd be right alongside him
just trying to keep up with him.
I don't think he ever knew
how proud I felt of him.
Or how good it felt
just to be there alongside him.
Even now, when I think back on it,
I still feel...
The thing is, Jess
I couldn't tell him about it then,
but I can tell you about it now.
I don't wanna wait 10 years to tell you
how I'm feeling about you right now.
Hello?
- Get a load of that!
- We had a blowout a while back.
Raunchy, very raunchy.
Is the motor okay?
Yeah, the motor's fine.
Look, about this tire...
Don't do much work on these myself,
except to scrape them off the road.
- Yeah. Hey, how about this tire, huh?
- Have it fixed in no time.
I can sell you a set of Dunlops
for next to nothing.
- No, thanks.
- I can't remember where I got them,
but I got them, know what I mean?
No, we'll be all right
just as soon as we get this fixed.
- Max?
- Yeah?
Listen
Sproggo's talked me
into buying him an ice cream, so
I think I'll see you later.
Sure, there's a shop just down the beach.
They'll appreciate the business.
Sure, thanks.
Toodle pip.
Bye.
You just trucking around?
Good time for just trucking.
Wish I could do a bit myself.
Which way you heading? North?
Uh, maybe.
Look what's turned up for Sunday dinner.
Main course and dessert.
My favorite kind
female.
Mm.
Watch the tongue, sweetheart.
I've seen him lick his eyebrow clean.
You must've spent some loot.
Like the sign says,
speed's just a question of money.
How fast do you wanna go?
- Max, quick, get in.
- What's wrong?
Just take my word for it, get in!
- What about the tire?
- Please, Max!
Your tire, man!
Hey, fella!
Watch your tire!
Crazy people!
The world's full of crazy people.
That wagon, was it here?
Sure, a couple with a kid.
- Who are they?
- I was just fixing their tire.
They left their goddamn spare.
Not a bad one either. Ha, ha.
- Who are they?
- A couple
passing through.
Said they were heading north. Maybe.
You want to drive the car? No?
You'd rather play with the ball?
Into the back.
There you go.
I can still see his face now.
Looked as if he'd just swallowed a brick.
What a mean old lady you are.
Huh, Sproggy?
- That's enough from you, mate!
- The dog.
What's the matter with you?
What you got there, pal?
Max!
Yeah, yeah, that's the way I see it too.
Yep. Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Sure. It's been nice talking to you. Bye.
Take it you agreed with him.
- If they're not worried, I'm not.
- What about that?
I figure it's lost property.
If no one makes a claim to it,
I say we can forget it.
Sounds okay to me, Jess.
Don't know.
If Ziggy says so, believe me, it's okay.
Now, May's expecting you up at the farm.
You'll have no more trouble up there.
Just green grass and fat cows.
- How are you doing?
- Mm. I'm getting there.
I reckon you ought to connect
the doohickey to the gizmo.
Come here, you.
You touch me with those hands
and I'll rip you apart. No!
No, look at them!
- No! No!
- You gonna give me a hug?
No, no...
May told me about the little beach
down by the trees.
- Mm.
- Do you want to come?
Love to
except that I've gotta fix the fan belt,
or we're never gonna get out of here.
Okay, Tarzan,
I'll bring you back some bananas.
All right.
Hey!
Jessie. If you meet Benno down there,
don't let him bother you.
He's only a baby.
Sure, May.
Here, boy.
Jessie, Jessie, wait a minute.
Calm down, now,
and tell me what's the matter.
Very, very naughty.
- Now you tell May what you...
- May.
May, you go and call Ziggy.
Call Ziggy,
and tell him to get here
as fast as he can.
Why, what's going on?
I think we've got some biker trouble.
It's gonna be all right.
Come on, darling. Come on, Jessie.
Well, let's go into the house.
It's gonna be all right.
You've had an awful time, darling,
but it's all over now.
Everything's going to be all right.
I've just got to go
and make a phone call,
and then we'll have
a nice hot cup of tea, huh?
Get me Ziggy, and hurry it up, will you?
It's May Swaisey.
Sprog? Oh, no.
Sprog?
Sprog!
Well, well.
It's our little mother.
That there is Cundalini,
and Cundalini wants his hand back.
I... I want my baby.
Tell you what
I'll swap you.
- Please, give me my baby.
- Jessie.
Jessie, Jessie.
You've not got a sense of humor.
You've got a pretty face, though,
awful pretty.
Yeah, awful pretty.
I suppose you don't need
a sense of humor with a pretty face.
The only trouble is though, missy
if you should
lose the face...
Please, don't hurt my baby.
- ...you've got nothing!
- What do you want from me?
- Don't change the subject.
- Hold it!
- Right there!
- Aah!
- I hate guns.
- Old lady.
Stand back!
- Stay back!
- Woman!
Stay back!
Anyone so much as breathes
I'll cream them!
Open that door.
You get over there.
Put the baby on the ground.
Jessie!
Get the van.
- Gate!
- Don't stop. Just go right through.
Now what?!
- The motor!
- What are you trying to say?
I don't know, it just died on me.
No! Run!
Oh.
No, Jessie!
Lord have mercy!
What do you think?
I'm a doctor, not a fortuneteller.
This your subdural?
- Yes, that's her.
- Lot of problems, huh?
Multiple traumas, spleen,
liver, lung, flail chest
left neck of femur, renal shutdown.
Reads like a grocery list.
She salvageable?
Yeah, sure, we got
all her signs back last night.
- Relatives?
- The husband.
They lost the kid. DOA.
Listen, tell him she's going to
be all right. Tell him not to worry.
If he wants, I'll talk to him.
I don't think he wants to talk to anyone.
He's been standing there
like a zombie all day.
Bubba Zanetti, is that you?
You come for the scooter?
She won't be ready until this afternoon.
Still having trouble with the front forks.
They're mothers to work with.
Hey!
You asshole! What the molly frock
do you think you're doing?
You and me are gonna talk
about the Toecutter.
Never heard of him. Aah!
What the Christ?
I want to know about the Toecutter.
I mind my own business, don't I?
I mean, they'd kill me if I didn't.
I'll say the names and
you say "yes" or "no."
- Nightrider.
- Yeah.
- The Toecutter.
- Bubba Zanetti.
- Yes!
There's more?
- They took Johnny.
- Johnny the Boy?
- Yeah. Some others.
- Where?
Out at the beaches, looking for fuel.
Are they coming back?
I don't know.
They got their bikes.
I don't know anymore.
Locate black Pursuit Special.
Unauthorized use by a Main Force officer.
Quit toying, Bubba.
Easy. I know what I'm doing.
Hi.
Hey, man. This...
This isn't what it looks, man.
You know, I... I just came down here
to check it out, and
this guy has already been snuffed.
Nothing you could do for him.
Ankle.
It's okay.
What are you doing, man?
Careful, my ankle! My foot, man!
Hey, listen, I had nothing to do
with anything going on back there, man.
Hey, listen, man, will you?
Listen to me!
Will you listen to me? They were
a hell of a crazy people back there, man.
Some kind of bad people.
I'm not responsible for anything.
Ow. What are you doing?
What are you doing, man?
What do you say?
What are you doing?
Hey, listen, I'm not a bad man.
I'm sick, see? Sick.
What do you call it?
Psychopathic, you know.
Personality disorder.
The judge, man, he said so.
You're not gonna hurt me, are you?
Jesus! You can't kill me!
Not for stealing a man's boots!
He was dead, for Christ sakes!
He won't need them anymore!
What are you doing?
I wanna know what you're doing.
The chain in those handcuffs
is high-tensile steel.
It'd take you 10 minutes
to hack through it with this.
Now, if you're lucky
you could hack through your ankle
in five minutes.
You're mad, man!
You think I look silly, don't you?
Don't bring this on me, man.
Don't do this to me!
Please, sweet Jesus. I was sick!
Don't bring this on me, please!